cssigniter.com 2016-11-15

# Privacy Policy – CSSIgniter - Premium WordPress Themes

Protecting your privacy and the information you provide us is a top priority for CSSIgniter LLC (“CSSIgniter”). By visiting our Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Any information submitted to CSSIgniter, is collected, managed and retained by CSSIgniter. Please be aware that your access to our Services may be subject to certain third party terms and conditions and privacy policies, including but not limited to third party payment processors. You agree that CSSIgniter is not liable for any such third party terms and conditions and their use of your personal information (information related to you that can identify you). We do not transfer, sell or rent your personal information to third parties in any way other than what is stated in this Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, this Privacy Policy only deals with the use and communication of information collected by CSSIgniter.

Those Privacy Policy provisions are part of our T[erms & Conditions](https://www.cssigniter.com/ignite/terms-conditions/)

#### 1\. What information is collected

Only registered Users may purchase a WordPress theme on our Website. Once you are registered, you have your own account (“Account”). You may register on our Website by providing the following personal information:  
– your first and last name  
– your e-mail address  
– your username  
– your password

You consent to our access to and collection of such personal information about you.

Once you are registered, you may login to your Account with your username and password. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your password and Account. You are fully responsible for all activities that occur under this Account and any other actions taken in connection with this Account. You must immediately notify CSSIgniter of any unauthorized uses of your Account or any other breaches of security. CSSIgniter will not be liable for any acts or omissions by you, including any damages of any kind incurred as a result of such acts or omissions. During the sign-up process, you may also select the option of receiving e-mail offers from us.

You have the obligation to state truthfully, accurately and completely your up-to-date personal information in the registration process and update your account whenever it is needed. If your personal information is not in compliance with these provisions or if CSSIgniter has reasonable suspicions that your personal information is not in accordance with these provisions, CSSIgniter has the right to reject your application for registration or to suspend or terminate immediately your Account, irrespectively of any notice, any use, current or future. In this case, you have no right to any refund for the suspension or termination of your Account.

#### 2\. How the information is used

CSSIgniter treats all personal information according to EU law or the law in the country in which you reside or operate (whichever applies). We collect two types of information from you: a) personal information as described above in paragraph 1 and b) non-personal information such as website navigation data. We do not transfer, sell or rent your personal information to third parties in any way other than what is stated in this Privacy Policy. We request only the personal information that we need to operate our Services and improve our Website’s user experience. We do not use your personal information to create any advertising creative.

We partner with third-party advertising networks to either display advertising on our Website or to manage our advertising on other sites. These ad network partners do not collect and do not have access to any personally identifiable information. They may, however, anonymously track your internet usage as described below in paragraph 6.

a) We may use your personal information for the following purposes:  
• Use of your e-mail associated with your Account in order to send you one newsletter per month in conjunction with your use of our Services. If you do not wish to receive newsletters you may unsubscribe by clicking the unsubscription link in the newsletter e-mail.  
• Use of your e-mail to send you system e-mails that you cannot opt out from and you will have to receive if you want to use our Website. If you want to stop receiving the system e-mails, you will have to opt-out by accessing your your Account at [Members’ section.](https://www.cssigniter.com/members/)  
b) CSSIgniter uses website navigation data to operate and improve the Website. CSSIgniter may also use website navigation data alone or in combination with your personal information to provide aggregated information about CSSIgniter.  
c) We store all the information that is tracked through standard Google Analytics but we do not save this information on our databases.

All the information, described in this paragraph 2, shall be used in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. We do not use your personal information in any other context other than the one described in our [Terms & Conditions](https://www.cssigniter.com/ignite/terms-conditions/) and Privacy Policy.

#### 3\. How your information is protected

a) To protect our Users’ privacy, Users’ personal information is not published in any way to other Users or third parties.  
b) CSSIgniter reserves its right though to share your personal information to a third party in case of sale merger, control change, reorganization or liquidation of the Company. All such actions shall be completed in compliance with applicable laws of personal data and privacy.  
c) We do not make any personal information available to third parties for their marketing purposes.  
d) If however, we share your personal information and data with third parties, we will notify you. Please note that no transmission over the internet can be fully guaranteed in its confidentiality and non-disclosure, and as such, you transmit at your own risk.  
e) CSSIgniter uses robust security measures to protect personal information from unauthorized access, maintain personal information accuracy, and help ensure the appropriate use of personal information. When the Services are accessed using the internet, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects your data using both server authentication and data encryption. These technologies help ensure that your information is safe, secure, and only available to you to whom the information belongs and those to whom you have granted access. CSSIgniter also implements other advanced technology measures to prevent interference or access from outside intruders.  
f) We do not tolerate Spam. To report CSSIgniter-related spam please contact us at info [] cssigniter.com. You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our [Terms & Conditions](https://www.cssigniter.com/ignite/terms-conditions/). We may check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content of the Website, but we will not permanently store messages sent through these tools.  
g) CSSIgniter does its utmost to secure its information storage in order to protect confidentiality of your personal information against loss and interception by third parties. However, it is important to know that there is no zero-risk against loss or interception by others of your personal information. You are responsible for maintaining the security and confidentiality of your Account’s username and password.

#### 4\. How the information is stored

We save your personal information in our database in order to improve our Website’s and user experience and in accordance with our [Terms & Conditions](https://www.cssigniter.com/ignite/terms-conditions/). If you wish that your personal information be permanently deleted from our database when you stop using our Services, please notify us at info@cssigniter.com.

#### 5\. Third Party Payment Processor

We use a third-party payment processor, Fastspring.com (the “Payment Processor”), to bill Users. Each User can pay the fees due via our Website. The processing of payments shall be subject to the privacy policies of the Payment Processor (https://fastspringsoftware.com/privacy-policy.html) in addition to CSSIgniter’s Privacy Policy. We only collect the personal information stated in par. 1 of his Privacy Policy. Any additional information requested by the Payment Processor is collected and stored by the Payment Processor and not CSSIgniter. CSSIgniter does not collect nor store any credit card or other billing information. CSSIgniter stores only a User’s identification code to verify payment by a User, sent by the Payment Processor to CSSIgniter. We are not responsible for the use of your personal information by the Payment Processor.

#### 6\. Cookies Policy

CSSIgniter is using cookies to improve your experience of our Website. When you visit our Website, CSSIgniter servers send a cookie to your web browser. You can delete these cookies at any time. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify an individual. Cookies merely recognize the web browser.

Session Cookies: If you are using our Services and you choose to identify yourself to us, CSSIgniter uses session cookies containing encrypted information to allow CSSIgniter to uniquely identify you. Each time you log into the Services, a session cookie containing an encrypted, unique identifier that is tied to your account and is placed on your browser. These session cookies allow CSSIgniter to uniquely identify you when you are logged into the Services and download our themes and to process online data transactions and requests. Session cookies are required to use the Services.

#### 7\. Legal requests

We cooperate with law enforcement authorities, as well as with other third parties, to enforce laws, intellectual property rights and to prevent fraud. In response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can, and you authorize us to, disclose your name, e-mail address and Website use history, with or without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, we will not disclose your personal information to any law enforcement or other governmental officials without a subpoena or court order, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to protect our rights, enforce our policies, respond to claims that your use of our Services violates CSSIgniter policies or rights or others, or protect anyone’s rights, property or safety.

#### 8\. Consent

By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information and data as described in this Privacy Policy and our [Terms & Conditions](https://www.cssigniter.com/ignite/terms-conditions/).

#### 9\. Changes

If our Privacy Policy procedures change, we will post those changes immediately to our Website. Any such changes will be effective immediately from the time they are posted, unless otherwise stated in the change provision. E-mail notification will be sent to Users who request it.
